<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Total Bhakti</string>
    <string name="error_player">There was an error initializing the YouTubePlayer (%1$s)</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_tutorial">This is a demo which shows how to handle fullscreen behaviour. This activity has differents layouts for portrait, landscape and fullscreen. The user can enter fullscreen either by using the player controller or programmatically by the programmer (here using a button). If your activity does not have a landscape layout, you can choose to automatically enter fullscreen when the device is rotated to landscape orientation.</string>
    <string name="enter_fullscreen">Enter Fullscreen</string>
    <string name="landscape_fullscreen">Always fullscreen in landscape</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_demo_name">Custom Fullscreen Handling</string>
    <string name="try_again">Reconnect</string>
    <string name="AdUnitId">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="Disclaimer">This template for privacy policy and terms and conditions is provided on "AS IS" basis, without warranties or conditions of any kind, either expressed or implied. It is intended for you as an inspirational document and you may use it when compiling your own privacy policy. The developer of App Privacy Policy Generator does not take any responsibility for the legal consequences associated with the use of this privacy policy or terms and conditions, and I urge you to seek local legal advice ensuring compliance with all rules applicable for the users of your application. The developer of App Privacy Policy Generator can in no way be found liable for any direct or indirect damage or loss suffered by you due to the use of this document.</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy_P1">Anurag Kumar built the [App Name] app as an Ad Supported app. This SERVICE is provided by Anurag Kumar at no cost and is intended for use as is.This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at [App Name] unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy_P2">I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy_P3">Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory.This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy_P4">I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
